<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Myself</title>
    <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Myself</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 17:36:04 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Imparare Una Altra Lingua</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/imparare-una-altra-lingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 17:36:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/imparare-una-altra-lingua/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Per leggere questo saggio, vai a &lt;a href=&#34;https://substack.com/@kevinjonas/note/p-152249789&#34;&gt;QUESTO ARTICOLO&lt;/a&gt; in Substack.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Intersection of Art and Logic</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/misc/arts-logic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 18:37:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/misc/arts-logic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please go&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://open.substack.com/pub/kevinjonas/p/the-intersection-of-art-and-logic?r=386ho4&amp;amp;utm_campaign=postutm_medium=web&#34;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt; to read this article on Substack!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perché scrivere ci aiuta per migliorare le nostre idee?</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/come-scrivendo-ci-aiuta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 14:59:56 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/come-scrivendo-ci-aiuta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Per leggere questo saggio, vai a &lt;a href=&#34;https://substack.com/@kevinjonas/note/p-151949373&#34;&gt;QUESTO ARTICOLO&lt;/a&gt; in Substack.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>111524</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/111524/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:08:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/111524/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;la-settimana-scorsa&#34;&gt;La settimana scorsa&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;La settimana scorsa è stata così così. Generalmente, è media, perché c&amp;rsquo;é stato una cosa che veramente ha migliorato. Io lo mando adesso.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>November 10th, 2024</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/books/finite-and-infinite-games/111024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 20:36:24 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/books/finite-and-infinite-games/111024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, I read through sections (if you can call it that) one through fifteen of the book. I already read it before, but I was&#xA;surprised at the amount of new insight I was able to gain when I read it again. I took notes in my notebook. My notes include&#xA;summaries, as well as my own analysis. To maintain the value of this read, I will only include my own analysis and give context&#xA;when needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/misc/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:01:47 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/misc/about-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I am Kevin Johnson, a Senior Computer Engineering Major from Texas A&amp;amp;M University. I am interested in making the biggest impact on&#xA;the world and I am constantly looking for ways to achieve this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;College has potential to be an extremely transformative growth period in a lot of people’s lives. This certainly rang true for me,&#xA;because at Texas A&amp;amp;M University I’ve had several opportunities that developed me as a leader and problem solver. My involvement in&#xA;student organizations has given me opportunities to engage in several high-impact students that affect students all across Texas A&amp;amp;M&#xA;University. In addition, I also got to learn how much of an impact I can make through software and how fun developing mastery over&#xA;such a powerful tool is. I hope to utilize these leadership, interpersonal, and technical skills to help make the world a&#xA;better place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novo novembre, 2024</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/110924/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:39:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/italian/110924/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Voglio usare questo sito per scrivere in italiano. Oggi è un buon giorno. Ieri notte, mi sono divertito a casa di Cooper. Era il&#xA;cumpleanno di Cooper. Ho bevuto molto vino lí, ma ho potuto correre oggi mattina. Adesso, mi sto rilassando nel bar di POV e loro&#xA;stanno mettendo la musica natalizia. Non è sicuro se sia troppo presto per quello da allor è il nove novembre.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Summer Internship 2024</title>
      <link>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/misc/amazon-summer-internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:41:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archives.kjonasj.com/personal-websites/hugo/misc/amazon-summer-internship/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The period of time when I learned the most about Software Engineering was last summer, when I interned with Amazon. Since I believe in&#xA;high-impact ventures, I was extremely happy to play a huge role in ensuring an efficient transportation system for Amazon. With that&#xA;being said, there were several factors that made  this internship much more challenging than a typical Amazon internship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, I was expected to communicate with the product manager, who I was building the internal tool for, and an internatinal team&#xA;based out of India, who had the most up-to-date technical knowledge regarding this internal tool, in order to come up with a perfect&#xA;solution that improved Amazon’s business. I also was given an unique opportunity to build something from the ground up, meaning a lot&#xA;of advanced infrastructure set up regarding build systems, pipelines, etc. had to be handled by me. My mentor was also based out of&#xA;India, so I was also forced to research documentation and talk to others in order to come up with solutions on my own a lot of times.&#xA;I was also in the depths of Java and OOP, and this forced me to think a lot about code structure and how it is best done to ensure the&#xA;systems we build are the most maintainable and expandable. I saw OOP as not just a silly example in class, but rather as an actual&#xA;tool, that when used properly, helps manage complexity by developing abstractions that the next level can afford to not worry about.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
